justnaturalskincare.com 2010-01-03

# Privacy and Security at JustNaturalSkinCare website

We will never sell any information collected from our customers during the ordering process to Internet   
or direct mail services. You can shop at JustNaturalSkinCare.com with the full confidence that your   
personal and purchasing information will remain private.  
Our  highest priority is to provide our customers with a secure shopping environment.  
The shopping cart on JustNaturalSkincare.com  website which requires you to enter personal data   
such as your name, e-mail address, and credit card information is PROTECTED by the industry   
standard secure sockets layer encryption technology.  

**_Why we ask you to provide information_** When you purchase a product from JustNatural, we ask you to provide information required to fulfill   
your order. We do not require you to create an account to place an order,you may place an order as   
a Guest. You will need to provide your name, email address, phone, shipping address, and billing   
address in order to process an order. ** _We don't provide your information to a third party_** As a  customer, your email address and phone number will never be rented, sold, or provided to a third   
party. Occasionally, we make special offers available to our customers like promotions, sales, events,   
discounts, etc.  
You may periodically receive e-mail notification from us regarding these special events and offers. If   
you do not want to receive e-mail notification from us concerning special promotions, or new products   
simply use the "unsubscribe" link. Should you have questions about how we use your information, feel   
free to send us a message by visiting the Contact Us section of this Web site.

W

 _e also regularly aggregate our sales and market information based on our customers' purchases.  
_ We use this information to be certain that we are offering the right products at the right time. We like   
to understand what regions of the country buy more products from us, what products are the most   
popular, and generally how our business is doing. At no time is any personally identifiable information   
made available in these market aggregates. _Cookies  
_ We do employ cookies (a cookie is a piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server, and   
stored on your hard drive) to allow us to maintain products in your shopping cart as you explore   
various parts of our Web site. Cookies also allow us to know if you have visited our site before or if   
you are a first time visitor. This provides us with important marketing information and lets us know   
how we are doing at both attracting new visitors and maintaining relationships with our existing   
customers. Cookies are required to place an online order with us. _Secure Online Ordering  
_ We store only the information we require to fulfill your order.

Your personal and credit card information is encrypted during transmission through our Secure Socket   
Layer (SSL), and maintained in a secure database that is not connected to the Internet. Our Web site   
security and fulfillment processes have been reviewed and approved by VeriSign, an independent   
security accrediting group.

| | **  ** **P** **r** **ivacy** ** & ****Security**  
---|---|---  
| |   
  
We will never sell any information collected from our customers during the ordering process to Internet   
or direct mail services. You can shop at JustNaturalSkinCare.com with the full confidence that your   
personal and purchasing information will remain private.  
Our  highest priority is to provide our customers with a secure shopping environment.  
The shopping cart on JustNaturalSkincare.com  website which requires you to enter personal data   
such as your name, e-mail address, and credit card information is PROTECTED by the industry   
standard secure sockets layer encryption technology.  

We  collect  your e-mail address when you place an order, if you enter a contest or if you volunteer   
to join our Newsletter.  This address is used primarily to communicate with you about your order.  We   
also periodically send out informational and promotional newsletters.  If you provide your e-mail   
address, you are automatically added to that list. However, opting out of that list is as simple as   
clicking a link at the bottom of any e-mail you receive from us. By opting out, you are immediately and   
permanently removed from our list; unless and until you manually add yourself back in. Your e-mail   
address is not sold or given to any other companies or "partners".  

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data.   
Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If   
you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information   
about your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more information about how   
Yahoo! uses this information.  

We hope to bring the best services, and that you'll return often to visit and shop with us.  

**JustNaturalSkinCare** does not sell, rent or share any personal information about our customers to   
any third party. We realize that our customers trust us to protect their personal information. We take   
that task seriously. Your Credit Card information is protected with SSL encryption through our Secure   
server payment system ** _At no time will we ever release your credit card or personal information to anyone!  
_**

**Questions?  
**

If you have questions we are here to help. Leave us a detailed e-mail message by clicking   
here **COMMENTS / QUESTIONS  
** We'll respond as  soon as possible to help you with your concerns.  

**_Thank you for coming to visit._** _   
Since the beginning of our company, it has been our intention to provide  
the best  natural products by using only the finest ingredients regardless of cost.  
Our promise to you is that we will continue to use and seek out the best ingredients from around the   
world to make personal skin care products . With the intent to  have you as a loyal customer for life.  
_

Copyright © 1999-2008 JustNatural® LLC  
All Rights Reserved  

_____________________________________________________________________________________  

_____________________________________________________________________________________  

____________________________________________________________________________________  

All UPS Ground Shipping  $5.99  

_________________________________________________________________________________________________________________  

_________________________________________________________________________________________________________________
